NNAJI OBINNA JOHNSON

BUSINESS & DATA ANALYST



+234 -8100 -887-062



jobinnannaji@gmail.com



7a, Ranti-Alabi Street, Iyana-ipaja, Lagos state.



https://www.linkedin.com/in/obinna-nnaji-a64b8a216



https://roarnotes.github.io/ nnajiobinna

PROFILE

Versatile with experience in business intelligence and data analytics roles and tasks. Problem solving skills with a track record of delivering top quality results and on time.. I am competent and professional with a true desire to learn, grow, and deliver results.

SOFTWARE SKILLS

- Project planning
- Data collection
- Data modelling
- Data management
- Data visualizations
- Interactive dashboard design
- · Pattern and trends recognition
- Descriptive and diagnostic analysis
- Prescriptive and predictive analysis
- Data driven insights
- Proficiency with spreadsheets,
 SQL, R, SPSS, and Python
- Microsoft office

PERSONAL SKILLS

- Communication
- Presentation
- · Problem-solving
- Research
- Attention to detail

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE, AGRICULTURAL ECONOMICS. University of Nigeria, Nsukka 2015 - 2020

GOOGLE DATA ANALYTICS Coursera Online Courses June. 2023

GOOGLE BUSINESS INTELLIGENCE Coursera Online Courses June, 2023

EXPERIENCE

DATA & RESEARCH SPECIALIST Mich Tech Global

2020 - 2023

- Develop computer database, analyzing data sets, and reporting findings to clients
- Collecting data into databases and maintaining accurate data record information

ACCOUNT MANAGER New Crystal Communication Limited

2022 - 2023

- Conducting market research and identifying business opportunities and client service
- Assist in making the right advertising choices and choosing the right media spots

DATA & RESRACH PERSONNEL Dabur International Limited 2019

- Collect data from distributors and wholesaler-consumers concerning company's products
- Provide trends from customer feedbacks to sales and marketing team

PERSONAL INFO

Sex: Male

Place of birth: Lagos State, Nigeria. State of Origin: Enugu State, Nigeria.

PERSONAL INTEREST

- Football
- · Travel and culture
- Reading books
- Charity

NNAJI OBINNA JOHNSON

BUSINESS & DATA ANALYST

NATIONAL YOUTH SERVICE CORP(NYSC)

Onitsha, Anambra State 2022 - 2023

REFERENCE

Provided upon request